<channel id="bbc2" source="XMLTV" date="28/03/2016">
<programme>
<desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two. [S]</desc>
<end>0610</end>
<title>This Is BBC Two</title>
<start>0530</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<type>Film</type>
<desc>
Drama set in 19th-century Paris telling the story of a rogue who exploits women to fulfil his aspirations to wealth and social status. Adapted from Guy de Maupassant's novel. [BandW, 1947] [S]
</desc>
<title>The Private Affairs of Bel Ami</title>
<end>0800</end>
<start>0610</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0800</start>
<end>0935</end>
<title>The Amazing Mr Blunden</title>
<desc>
Ghost story about two young children asked by ghost children to solve an ancient mystery, requiring them to travel back in time. [1972] [S]
</desc>
<type>Film</type>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0935</start>
<type>Film</type>
<desc>
Drama based on the true story of a thoroughbred racehorse. A housewife is forced to take over ownership of stables when her father becomes too sick to run the business. Also in HD. [2010] [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>Secretariat</title>
<end>1130</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
5/10. Wildlife cameraman Colin Stafford-Johnson revisits a gang of crested black macaques on the paradise Indonesian island of Sulawesi, 25 years after his first encounter. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<end>1230</end>
<title>Meet the Monkeys: Natural World</title>
<start>1130</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<type>Film</type>
<desc>
Historical epic starring Alec Guinness and Sophia Loren. After Marcus Aurelius is poisoned, his cruel son Commodus becomes emperor and quickly reveals a tyrannical streak. [1964] [S]
</desc>
<title>The Fall of the Roman Empire</title>
<end>1520</end>
<start>1230</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Series exploring Australia's coastline. Tim Flannery walks the Dinosaur Coast and Neil Oliver wrestles the southern hemisphere's biggest tides at Horizontal Falls. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>Coast Australia</title>
<end>1615</end>
<subtitle>The Kimberley</subtitle>
<start>1520</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1615</start>
<desc>
4/5. The Lea: Griff Rhys Jones meets the Sicilian cucumber-growing community of Essex, sails a gunpowder boat and trains with a team of veteran rowers as he explores the Lea. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<end>1715</end>
<title>Rivers with Griff Rhys Jones</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Jeremy Vine hosts the show where every day a new team of challengers take on what is probably the greatest quiz team in Britain, made up of some of the country's top quizzers. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Eggheads</title>
<end>1745</end>
<start>1715</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1745</start>
<desc>
11/20. Thomas Plant and Anita Manning tour the country in a yellow Lotus. Their first leg sees them start in Hertfordshire and work their way towards an auction in Banbury. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Antiques Road Trip</title>
<end>1830</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>1900</end>
<title>Too Much TV</title>
<desc>
21/25. Aled Jones and Sara Cox give the lowdown on everything you should be watching, report on the latest TV news and delve deep into the archives of the nation's best-loved shows. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>1830</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1900</start>
<title>This Farming Life</title>
<end>2000</end>
<desc>
10/12. A look at modern farming life in Scotland. In Argyll, Sybil prepares for George's 50th birthday. Bobby and Anne hold an open day to educate the public about farming. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
It's the last of the quarter-finals and one more team will make it through to the semi-final stage of the quiz for students. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>2030</end>
<title>University Challenge</title>
<start>2000</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2030</start>
<desc>
2/6. Your People Shall Be My People: Series following community life on Unst. Islanders Frank and Jem Roberts prepare their Shetland ponies for the prestigious pony assessment. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>An Island Parish: Shetland</title>
<end>2100</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2100</start>
<desc>
...American Crime Story. 7/10. Conspiracy Theories: The background to another iconic courtroom moment is exposed. Contains some strong language. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>The People v OJ Simpson:...</title>
<end>2140</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2140</start>
<desc>
...Sport Relief. Eddie Izzard attempts to run 27 marathons in 27 days for Sport Relief , marking the 27 years Nelson Mandela spent in prison. Contains some strong language. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>Eddie Izzard: Marathon Man for...</title>
<end>2240</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
16/16. Misconceptions: Quiz show in which the aim is to be interesting. Stephen Fry corrects some misconceptions with Sue Perkins, Sara Cox, Chris Addison and Alan Davies. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>QI XL</title>
<end>2325</end>
<start>2240</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
1/4. Donovan Bailey, Gareth Thomas, Iwan Thomas and James Toseland face a notorious fell run. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Natural Born Winners</title>
<end>0025</end>
<start>2325</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Behind Closed Doors</title>
<end>0125</end>
<desc>
Documentary giving an insight into domestic abuse, following the stories of three women over the course of 12 months. Contains strong language and disturbing scenes. [AD,S,SL]
</desc>
<start>0025</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0125</start>
<desc>
9/14. Puppet Up!: Teams must create two original characters for an improv comedy sketch in the Stuffed and Unstrung puppet show. Contains adult themes. [S,SL]
</desc>
<title>The Celebrity Apprentice USA</title>
<end>0250</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0250</start>
<title>Frankenstein and the Vampyre: A...</title>
<end>0350</end>
<desc>
...Dark and Stormy Night. Dramatised documentary exploring one of the most significant moments in gothic history. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0350</start>
<desc>
As Brazil prepares to host the World Cup, Copacabana Palace follows the lives of the staff and guests at one of Latin America's most iconic hotels. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<title>Copacabana Palace</title>
<end>0450</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0450</start>
<end>0600</end>
<title>This Is BBC Two</title>
<desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two. [S]</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
5/10. Artists from all over the UK compete for a spot at a grand exhibition and sale at the Royal College of Art in London. The judges examine the work of amateur sculptor Peter Gillies. [S]
</desc>
<end>0645</end>
<title>Show Me the Monet</title>
<start>0600</start>
</programme>
</channel>
