<channel id="cbbc" source="XMLTV" date="28/03/2016">
<programme>
<desc>
Welcome to the CBBC channel. Programmes start at 7.00am.
</desc>
<end>0700</end>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
<start>0530</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0700</start>
<title>Arthur</title>
<end>0715</end>
<subtitle>Muffy Takes the Wheel</subtitle>
<desc>
Animation following the adventures of a young aardvark and his friends. It's the first annual Lakewood Derby, but Muffy's dad takes over her project. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>0720</end>
<title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
<desc>
16/20. The Snapshot: Animated series set on a remote rural farm. The Farmer wants a family photo and instructs Bitzer to gather all the animals together. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>0715</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0720</start>
<desc>
Animated series. Danger Mouse is forced to choose between dedication to duty and friendship when he battles the Baron in his underwater Toadlantis base. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<subtitle>Danger at C Level</subtitle>
<title>Danger Mouse</title>
<end>0730</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0730</start>
<end>0740</end>
<title>New: Brain Freeze 2</title>
<subtitle>Space</subtitle>
<desc>
Doctor Knowles and Professor McCork get to the bottom of life's questions. Knowles and McCork ask the question 'What is a black hole?'. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0740</start>
<desc>Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<end>0745</end>
<title>Newsround</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0745</start>
<desc>
1/15. Gladiator Battle in Croatia: Series about unusual places in Europe. Ed Petrie and friends visit statues in Spain, an ice palace in Switzerland and an amphitheatre in Croatia. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>0815</end>
<title>All Over the Place: Europe</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<end>0825</end>
<title>Newsround</title>
<start>0815</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0825</start>
<desc>
Ricky draws and paints with his friends and family. Gav plays a prank on Ricky, so he decides to get his own back using six thousand cups of juice. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Art Ninja 2</title>
<end>0855</end>
<subtitle>Day of the Prank</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
1/10. A New Boy in Town: Documentary series following young ice skaters. The ice-dancing girls are desperate for boy partners - there's only one in the squad, and he's already taken. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>0925</end>
<title>Ice Stars</title>
<start>0855</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0925</start>
<desc>
Talent show. Eight young singers and their mums arrive at the music mansion where presenter Lauren Platt reveals the exciting prize that awaits at the end of the competition. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Got What It Takes?</title>
<end>1005</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
1/20. Lost and Found: Drama series. Bailey's world is rocked when his mum turns up at Ashdene Ridge. Can he forgive her for abandoning him as a toddler? Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<end>1035</end>
<title>The Dumping Ground</title>
<start>1005</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
1/15. The LA Arrival: Matilda Ramsay and her family head to Los Angeles, where Matilda takes over the kitchen and cooks some of the best and healthiest dishes for family and friends. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>1050</end>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<start>1035</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1050</start>
<end>1105</end>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<desc>
2/15. The Movies: Matilda Ramsay and her family head to Los Angeles, where they visit one of Hollywood's top stunt schools and learn how to make their own action films. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1105</start>
<desc>
1/6. Sapphire's Stir-Fry: Residents of the Dumping Ground reunite to cook fun and tasty recipes. In this episode, Lily cooks Sapphire's stir-fry. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>The Dumping Ground Dish Up</title>
<end>1110</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
3/15. The Monster Party: Matilda Ramsay and her family are in LA to make food and have fun. Matilda creates a ghoulish menu with severed hands, goblin heads and bloody cakes. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<end>1125</end>
<start>1110</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
4/15. The Beach BBQ: Matilda Ramsay and her family are in LA to make food and have fun. Matilda cooks garlic bread, a clam bake and an American BBQ classic at the beach. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<end>1140</end>
<start>1125</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>The Dumping Ground Dish Up</title>
<end>1145</end>
<desc>
2/6. Frank's Meatballs: Residents of the Dumping Ground reunite to cook fun and tasty recipes. In this episode, Sapphire cooks Frank's meatballs. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>1140</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1145</start>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<end>1200</end>
<desc>
5/15. The Big Food Fight: Matilda Ramsay and her family are in LA to make food and have fun. Matilda and the Ramsay bunch set up a food face-off - British versus American. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1200</start>
<type>Film</type>
<desc>
Family animation. When the Boogeyman lays down the gauntlet to take over the world, the immortal Guardians must join forces for the first time. [2012] [AD,S]
</desc>
<end>1330</end>
<title>Rise of the Guardians</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1330</start>
<desc>
Iain Stirling hosts the school-based comedy panel show. He is joined by special guests Hacker the Dog, Susan Calman, Steve Bugeja and Ben Shires. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<title>New: The Dog Ate My Homework</title>
<end>1400</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1400</start>
<title>Operation Ouch!</title>
<end>1425</end>
<desc>
Dr Chris and Dr Xand reveal the surprising secret behind the speed of your nerves, and Dr Xand finds out what happens if you don't wash your hands. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1425</start>
<title>Ice Stars</title>
<end>1455</end>
<desc>
1/10. A New Boy in Town: Nine-year-old Charlie attempts to impress the ice hockey coach. Also in HD. [S,SL]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
A new patisserie opens in Beanotown right opposite Pieface's dad's pie shop - and the crafty owner is determined to put his rival out of business. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<subtitle>Pie Protectors</subtitle>
<end>1510</end>
<title>Dennis the Menace and Gnasher</title>
<start>1455</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1510</start>
<end>1520</end>
<title>Sidekick</title>
<subtitle>Days of Golly</subtitle>
<desc>
Animated series following four friends as they train at the Academy for Aspiring Sidekicks. The kids try to help the Golly Gee Kid relive his glory days. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1520</start>
<desc>
Animated series. The world is in jeopardy and the only thing that can save it is a 1,000ft Penfold. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
<end>1530</end>
<title>Danger Mouse</title>
<subtitle>Big Penfold</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Animated series. A dragon-hunting expedition leads Ant to find an ancient scroll that holds clues to an amazing mystery. But his family are trapped by the dragon. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>1555</end>
<title>The Deep</title>
<subtitle>Here Be Dragons</subtitle>
<start>1530</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1555</start>
<desc>
31/34. What Are You Waiting For?: Michelle is pitted against Amanda in the female solo round. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<end>1620</end>
<title>The Next Step</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>1625</end>
<title>Newsround</title>
<desc>Topical news magazine for children. [S]</desc>
<start>1620</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>1640</end>
<title>Is Tech Taking Over? - A...</title>
<desc>
...Newsround Special. Ricky Boleto investigates the role technology plays in our lives, and what would happen if we weren't allowed to use our gadgets anymore. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>1625</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Matilda and the Ramsay Bunch</title>
<end>1700</end>
<desc>
8/15. The Sleepover: Matilda tries to banish the boys and have a girls-only sleepover. Megan, Holly and their friend Elspeth head off to check out the night stars at a planetarium. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>1640</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1700</start>
<title>New: Pocket Money Pitch</title>
<end>1730</end>
<desc>
8/10. Animal Innovations: Six young entrepreneurs pitch their ideas to a Claire Gavin, head of products and innovation at the UK's largest pet retailer. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1730</start>
<end>1800</end>
<title>The Dumping Ground</title>
<desc>
19/20. Coming Round: Drama series. Jody upsets Ryan, and when May-Li's grandmother turns up unexpectedly, Ryan sees his chance to take cruel revenge during a martial arts battle. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Animated series. Ant and Fontaine hunt for the rarest of ocean creatures, the colossal squid. But it turns out to be smarter than them and thinks they look tasty. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<subtitle>Colossal Squid</subtitle>
<end>1820</end>
<title>New: The Deep</title>
<start>1800</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Dragons - Riders of Berk</title>
<end>1845</end>
<desc>
5/20. In Dragons We Trust: Animation based on How to Train Your Dragon. The dragons are blamed for an outbreak of crime. Also in HD. [S]
</desc>
<start>1820</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1845</start>
<subtitle>Oppoxox</subtitle>
<end>1858</end>
<title>Sidekick</title>
<desc>
Animated series following four friends as they train at the Academy for Aspiring Sidekicks. Master XOX turns into a good guy and Splittsboro goes haywire. Also in HD. [AD,S]
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc/>
<title>..programmes start at 7.00am</title>
<end>0058</end>
<start>1858</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0058</start>
<end>0530</end>
<title>..programmes start at 7.00am</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>This is CBBC!</title>
<end>0700</end>
<desc>
Welcome to the CBBC channel. Programmes start at 7.00am.
</desc>
<start>0530</start>
</programme>
</channel>
