<channel id="five" source="XMLTV" date="28/03/2016">
<programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>
Alien animation. The WotWots are sailing paper boats on a pond when SpottyWot's boat suddenly sinks. He thinks he spots the culprit, but what sort of creature is it? (S2 Ep 6)
</desc>
<title>The WotWots</title>
<end>0610</end>
<subtitle>Swan Lake</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Animation. Chloe and her pals have to deliver a new magic lamp to Mrs Genie, but they accidentally use up its three wishes! (S1 Ep 29)
</desc>
<subtitle>Extra Special Delivery</subtitle>
<title>Chloe's Closet</title>
<end>0620</end>
<start>0610</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0620</start>
<desc>
Animation. A barometer washes up on the beach and warns of a storm. Salty leads everyone to shelter, but when Puffin opens the door they all get a big surprise. (S1 Ep 32)
</desc>
<title>Driftwood Bay</title>
<end>0630</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0630</start>
<title>Fireman Sam</title>
<end>0640</end>
<subtitle>Baa Baa Baby</subtitle>
<desc>
Animation. Everyone mistakes Lambikins for a real baby when Sarah wraps up Woolly's new lamb for a walk in the pram after the boiler in the Wholefish Cafe breaks down. (S6 Ep 8)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Wissper</title>
<end>0650</end>
<desc>
CGI-animation. Beavers Ed and Ted can't agree on the final part of their new dam, so Wissper asks cool dude Kev the crocodile to help. (Ep 29)
</desc>
<start>0640</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0650</start>
<desc>
Animated series about a lovable little pig. Daddy teaches Peppa and George a fun game to play while they wait inside for the rain to stop. (S4 Ep 9)
</desc>
<subtitle>The Rainy Day Game</subtitle>
<end>0655</end>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0655</start>
<subtitle>Pasty's Backpack</subtitle>
<title>Pip Ahoy!</title>
<end>0710</end>
<desc>
Children's animation about a young puppy named Pip and his friend Alba. A storm spreads Pasty's collection of things all over the beach. (S1 Ep 30)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Little Princess</title>
<end>0720</end>
<subtitle>I Want to Go to the Fair</subtitle>
<desc>
Julian Clary narrates an animation based on the picture books. Little Princess is off to the fair, but in her excitement, she ends up hurting her foot. (S2 Ep 4)
</desc>
<start>0710</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>0735</end>
<title>Bob the Builder</title>
<desc>
CGI animation. Bob and the team are building the set for the new movie 'Space Robots 3D', but Leo's acting aspirations cause problems for the film's stars. (S1 Ep 24)
</desc>
<start>0720</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0735</start>
<desc>
Train fun. Thomas is working with Whiff the Rubbish Engine today, but how can he freshen up later to take the Duchess of Boxford to tea? (S16 Ep 7)
</desc>
<subtitle>Thomas and the Rubbish Train</subtitle>
<title>Thomas and Friends</title>
<end>0750</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0750</start>
<end>0800</end>
<title>Noddy in Toyland</title>
<subtitle>The Fastest Trousers</subtitle>
<desc>
When Mr Plod accidentally spills some 'go faster' dust on his trousers, they zoom off on their own. Can Noddy and Mr Whiz's Suck-o-Matic save the day? (S1 Ep 16)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0800</start>
<desc>
Impish animation. King Thistle is snowed under with royal duties. He must launch a boat, judge a competition and make a speech at a festival. Can Holly help? (S1 Ep 8)
</desc>
<subtitle>The King's Busy Day</subtitle>
<end>0815</end>
<title>Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0815</start>
<end>0825</end>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<subtitle>Grampy Rabbit's Lighthouse</subtitle>
<desc>
Pig tales. Grandpa Pig takes Peppa, George and Danny Dog to visit Grampy Rabbit's lighthouse. (S1 Ep 46)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0825</start>
<desc>
Pig tales. Miss Rabbit has hurt her ankle, so her sister and her friends offer to fill in for her at the ice cream stand. (S3 Ep 37)
</desc>
<end>0835</end>
<title>Peppa Pig</title>
<subtitle>Miss Rabbit's Day Off</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
CGI animated series about a pack of puppies led by a 10-year-old boy named Ryder. A baby elephant escapes when the circus comes to town. (S1 Ep 13)
</desc>
<subtitle>Pups Save the Circus</subtitle>
<title>Paw Patrol</title>
<end>0850</end>
<start>0835</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0850</start>
<subtitle>The Housesitters</subtitle>
<end>0900</end>
<title>Bananas in Pyjamas</title>
<desc>
Animated series. When the Teddies ask the Bananas to house-sit, they find a leaking tap which they resolve to fix. But their efforts just create a huge flood. (S1 Ep 92)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>0915</end>
<title>Toot the Tiny Tugboat</title>
<desc>
Animated series. Things are going missing around the Harbour, so Toot learns how to become a detective in order to solve the mystery. (S1 Ep 30)
</desc>
<start>0900</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>Matthew Wright hosts the topical discussion show.</desc>
<end>1130</end>
<title>The Wright Stuff: Easter Special</title>
<start>0915</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>1200</end>
<title>Funniest Fails, Falls and Flops</title>
<desc>
Clip show. Highlights include a young woman practising yoga too close to the waves, a junior weightlifter smashing his fishtank and people putting the 'break' into dancing. (S1 Ep 3)
</desc>
<start>1130</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<subtitle>Fleet</subtitle>
<title>Cowboy Builders</title>
<end>1255</end>
<desc>
Dom and Melinda come to the aid of a single mum in Fleet, who has been left with a house that is not fit for human habitation. (S6 Ep 12)
</desc>
<start>1200</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1255</start>
<desc>National and international news.</desc>
<end>1300</end>
<title>5 News At Lunchtime</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1300</start>
<desc>
Hunter says goodbye to his mother. Andy reveals that he knows Hunter started the fire and proposes they frame Charlotte. Ash is thrown when Phoebe tells him she still loves him.
</desc>
<end>1330</end>
<title>Home and Away</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1330</start>
<end>1400</end>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<desc>
Sonya receives an ominous photograph of Nell. Brodie prepares to leave after a bad training session with Brad. Aaron is humiliated after realising that Tom was using him.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1400</start>
<desc>
Crime spin-off series. The team cross swords with the Triads when they try to stop the flow of a deadly hallucinogen that is threatening to flood the city. (S2 Ep 6)
</desc>
<title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
<end>1455</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>1745</end>
<title>The Dirty Dozen</title>
<desc>
War drama starring Lee Marvin and Ernest Borgnine. A motley crew of death-row criminals get the chance to redeem themselves in action on a suicide mission. (1967)
</desc>
<type>Film</type>
<start>1455</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1745</start>
<title>5 News</title>
<end>1800</end>
<desc>National and international news.</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Sonya receives an ominous photograph of Nell. Brodie prepares to leave after a bad training session with Brad. Aaron is humiliated after realising that Tom was using him.
</desc>
<title>Neighbours</title>
<end>1830</end>
<start>1800</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Hunter says goodbye to his mother. Andy reveals that he knows Hunter started the fire and proposes they frame Charlotte. Ash is thrown when Phoebe tells him she still loves him.
</desc>
<title>Home and Away</title>
<end>1900</end>
<start>1830</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1900</start>
<end>2000</end>
<title>Inside Buckingham Palace</title>
<desc>
Two-part series exploring one of the most famous buildings in the world. A look at the years since the Queen ascended to the throne and look ahead to what might become of it. (Ep 1)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
With the help of previously unseen documents including secret letters to the former Edward VIII, this episode looks at some of the stormier years experienced at the Palace. (Ep 2)
</desc>
<end>2100</end>
<title>Inside Buckingham Palace</title>
<start>2000</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2100</start>
<title>New: The Tube: Going Underground</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>
Documentary series. At Victoria, the closure of the ticket office creates problems and 72-year-old customer service assistant Philippa calls it a day. (Ep 2)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Drama series set in pre-Batman Gotham City. A skilled cryogenics engineer named Victor Fries goes on a body-snatching spree while the Penguin heads to Arkham. (S2 Ep 12)
</desc>
<title>New: Gotham: Wrath Of The Villains</title>
<end>2255</end>
<start>2200</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2255</start>
<title>Goal Rush: Football League Tonight</title>
<end>0000</end>
<desc>Highlights from SkyBet League 1 and 2. (S1 Ep 37)</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Drama. Samaritan launches a cyber-attack on the stock exchange, leaving the team with no choice but to embark on a mission to stop a global economic catastrophe. (S4 Ep 11)
</desc>
<end>0050</end>
<title>New: Person of Interest</title>
<start>0000</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<subtitle>Frenzy</subtitle>
<end>0115</end>
<title>True Crimes: The First 72 Hours</title>
<desc>
Award-winning part-dramatised crime documentary series based on real cases from across Canada and the USA.
</desc>
<start>0050</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>SuperCasino</title>
<end>0310</end>
<desc>
Live interactive gaming featuring roulette, blackjack and autowheel. For more information and to register visit SuperCasino.com.
</desc>
<start>0115</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<subtitle>A Deadly Affair</subtitle>
<end>0400</end>
<title>Castle</title>
<desc>
The US mystery series about a top crime writer who turns sleuth. Castle must prove his innocence when police find him standing over a dead woman, holding a gun. (S3 Ep 1)
</desc>
<start>0310</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0400</start>
<desc>
Documentary series about the work of dedicated animal lovers who save injured and orphaned wild animals brought into their sanctuary. (S3 Ep 5)
</desc>
<end>0420</end>
<title>Wildlife SOS</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0420</start>
<title>Great Artists</title>
<end>0445</end>
<desc>
Tim Marlow looks at the western world's most famous artists. Featuring the work of Giotto di Bondone, the Tuscan artist whose religious paintings transformed the genre. (S1 Ep 1)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0445</start>
<end>0510</end>
<title>House Doctor</title>
<desc>
Home improvement series. Californian real-estate agent Ann Maurice and Alistair Appleton tackle a three-storey stone cottage in Chippenham, Wiltshire. (S3 Ep 16)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<end>0535</end>
<title>House Doctor</title>
<desc>
Home improvement series. Californian interior designer Ann Maurice and Alistair Appleton tackle a property in Dulwich. (S3 Ep 17)
</desc>
<start>0510</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Home improvement series. Californian interior designer Ann Maurice works her magic on a house in Ashover Hay. (S3 Ep 18)
</desc>
<end>0600</end>
<title>House Doctor</title>
<start>0535</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>The WotWots</title>
<end>0610</end>
<subtitle>Wheelie Wots</subtitle>
<desc>
Alien animation. SpottyWot decides that the WotWots' spaceship needs new wheels, so he goes in search of different kinds of wheel around the farm. (S2 Ep 7)
</desc>
<start>0600</start>
</programme>
</channel>
