<channel id="ch4" source="XMLTV" date="28/03/2016">
<programme>
<title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
<end>0625</end>
<subtitle>Blitzgiving</subtitle>
<desc>
A broken oven forces the gang to spend Thanksgiving at Zoey's house, but it isn't long before she and Ted are at loggerheads once again.
</desc>
<start>0600</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0625</start>
<desc>
Adam and his friends go on a treasure hunt inspired by comedy adventure film The Goonies when Pops misplaces some family jewels. (S1 Ep16/23)
</desc>
<subtitle>Goldbergs Never Say Die!</subtitle>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>0650</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0650</start>
<end>0715</end>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<subtitle>Lame Gretzky</subtitle>
<desc>
Murray struggles to get Adam interested in hockey. Beverly tries to help Erica prepare for her college entrance exams, but her plans backfire. (S1 Ep17/23)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0715</start>
<desc>
Beverly replaces Murray's favourite chair with a new one without consulting him first. Adam is picked on during the bus ride to school. (S1 Ep18/23)
</desc>
<title>The Goldbergs</title>
<end>0740</end>
<subtitle>For Your Own Good</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Ray and Debra reminisce about how they first met 15 years earlier, including the first time Ray sampled Debra's cooking.
</desc>
<subtitle>How They Met</subtitle>
<end>0810</end>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
<start>0740</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0810</start>
<title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
<end>0840</end>
<subtitle>B**b Job</subtitle>
<desc>
Debra decides to conduct an experiment after seeing Ray's reaction to her friend's new and improved breasts.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0840</start>
<desc>
Frasier hopes to stop Eddie from putting himself about after he finds himself foster-father to a litter of puppies sired by the mutt.
</desc>
<subtitle>The Unkindest Cut of All</subtitle>
<end>0910</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0910</start>
<end>0940</end>
<title>Frasier</title>
<subtitle>The Matchmaker</subtitle>
<desc>
Frasier invites the new station manager home for dinner to fix him up with Daphne. But he thinks it's Frasier who's interested in him.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0940</start>
<desc>
Sheldon has to go back to Texas when his sister goes into labour, and while he is away the gang gather at the flat to decorate the Christmas tree. (S7 Ep11/24)
</desc>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1010</end>
<subtitle>The Cooper Extraction</subtitle>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Penny's big TV acting break hits the cutting room floor so Leonard does his best to comfort her, which leads her to ask him a bold question. (S7 Ep12/24)
</desc>
<title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
<end>1040</end>
<subtitle>The Hesitation Ramification</subtitle>
<start>1010</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
The perfect storm hits Springfield causing the Simpson roof to leak. Marge isn't happy, so Homer takes a stab at fixing things up, only to fall through the roof.
</desc>
<end>1110</end>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<subtitle>Don't Fear the Roofer</subtitle>
<start>1040</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
When new vending machines are installed at school, Bart becomes a junk food junkie, leading to massive weight gain and a heart attack.
</desc>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<end>1140</end>
<subtitle>The Heartbroke Kid</subtitle>
<start>1110</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1140</start>
<end>1310</end>
<title>A Goofy Movie</title>
<type>Film</type>
<year>1995</year>
<desc>
Animated Disney adventure. Goofy takes his wayward teenage son Max on a fishing holiday after he gets into trouble at school. But Max is more interested in going to a rock gig.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1310</start>
<desc>
Daniel Halley and Emma Greenfield want to find out what £73,000 can buy them on the Canary Island of Fuerteventura. Jasmine Harman shows them a selection of what's on the market.
</desc>
<title>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun</title>
<end>1410</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1410</start>
<end>1510</end>
<title>Deal or No Deal</title>
<desc>
Noel Edmonds presents the hit show in which players could win up to 250 grand. Players can also boost their money with Box 23 - but are they brave enough to buy it with their winnings?
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Mark Foster is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent.
</desc>
<end>1600</end>
<title>Countdown</title>
<start>1510</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1600</start>
<desc>
In France, the race is on to create a perfect shabby chic BandB before a big booking arrives, and tensions rise in Spain as two bar owners work together for the very first time.
</desc>
<end>1700</end>
<title>A New Life in the Sun</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1700</start>
<desc>
There's competitive piñata bashing and large helpings of frank feedback in this new episode from Marbella.
</desc>
<end>1800</end>
<title>Couples Come Dine with Me</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Homer misses a Moe's Tavern sponsored trip to Las Vegas to drive Bart to a juvenile delinquent camp. Meanwhile, Marge gets into trouble at a car boot sale.
</desc>
<subtitle>We're on the Road to D'oh-where</subtitle>
<end>1830</end>
<title>The Simpsons</title>
<start>1800</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>1830</start>
<end>1900</end>
<title>Hollyoaks</title>
<desc>
It's a race against time for Holly as she puts her life in danger to follow her heart. Robbie and Jason have an important decision to make, and hot newcomer Liam sets pulses galloping.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>Includes sport and weather.</desc>
<title>Channel 4 News</title>
<end>1915</end>
<start>1900</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
In an extraordinary live TV event, Guy Martin takes on his most daring and extreme world record attempt yet, as he defies gravity on the largest Wall of Death ever made.
</desc>
<title>Guy's Wall of Death: Live</title>
<end>2100</end>
<start>1915</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>The Island with Bear Grylls</title>
<end>2200</end>
<desc>
Bear Grylls abandons eight men and eight women on opposite sides of the same uninhabited tropical island to see if they can find food, water and shelter to survive. (S3 Ep1)
</desc>
<start>2100</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>2200</start>
<title>Fresh Meat</title>
<end>2250</end>
<desc>
The finals are over and the results are in, but not everyone's happy. Will the housemates host the best grad ball of all time or will they have to flee Manchester in the night? (S4 Ep6/6)
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Jimmy Carr hosts. Sean Lock and Kevin Bridges versus Jon Richardson and Rebecca Front. Joe Lycett is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent and Rachel Riley's on numbers and letters. (Ep4)
</desc>
<end>2350</end>
<title>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</title>
<start>2250</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>One Born Every Minute</title>
<end>0050</end>
<desc>
One Born Every Minute returns for a new series. Nineteen years after becoming the first triplet to be delivered at Liverpool Women's Hospital, Kirsty returns to have her own baby. (S9 Ep1)
</desc>
<start>2350</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
With Paloma Faith, Boy George, will.i.am and Ricky Wilson from The Voice; Jack Whitehall, Charlotte Ritchie, Joe Thomas and Greg McHugh from Fresh Meat; music from Years and Years. (Ep4/10)
</desc>
<end>0150</end>
<title>Alan Carr: Chatty Man</title>
<start>0050</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<desc>
Eric Casaburi, CEO of Retro Fitness, which offers a high-end gym experience to people at a low cost, poses incognito as a reality TV show contestant to work among his own staff.
</desc>
<end>0240</end>
<title>Undercover Boss USA</title>
<start>0150</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0240</start>
<subtitle>...Home</subtitle>
<end>0310</end>
<title>Sarah Beeny's How to Sell Your...</title>
<desc>
Sarah meets Alex and Charlotte in Morley, near Leeds, who need to sell or risk going bankrupt. In Cheltenham, Judith is putting her Victorian villa for sale online.
</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<title>Selling Houses with Amanda Lamb</title>
<end>0405</end>
<desc>
Three homeowners compete to sell their properties in Royton, near Oldham. One home needs more colour, another needs a lot less, and a third needs more living room space.
</desc>
<start>0310</start>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0405</start>
<desc>
Phil Spencer and Kirstie Allsopp help first-time buyer Zena Ellis, and new parents Lysan and Bo Cheng, with property searches in Luton and Bedfordshire. [SL]
</desc>
<end>0505</end>
<title>Location, Location, Location</title>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0505</start>
<end>0510</end>
<title>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</title>
<desc>Kirstie looks at upcycling in Bath.</desc>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0510</start>
<desc>
Noel Edmonds presents the hit show in which players could win up to 250 grand. Players can also boost their money with Box 23 - but are they brave enough to buy it with their winnings?
</desc>
<title>Deal or No Deal</title>
<end>0600</end>
</programme>
<programme>
<start>0600</start>
<desc>
Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Mark Foster is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent.
</desc>
<title>Countdown</title>
<end>0645</end>
</programme>
</channel>
